There's a signal bleeding through the walls tonight
오늘 밤, 벽을 뚫고 신호가 새어 나오네
A voice that lost its name before the morning light
동이 트기 전에 이름을 잃은 목소리
The dial keeps spinning past the empty bands
다이얼은 텅 빈 주파수 대역을 계속 지나가네
Where someone left a message no one understands
아무도 이해 못 할 메시지를 누군가 남겨둔 곳
And the wires remember what the world forgot
그리고 전선들은 세상이 잊은 것을 기억해
Every word still burning in a frequency left to rot
썩어가도록 방치된 주파수 속, 모든 단어들이 여전히 타올라
We were the broadcast no one tuned to hear
우리는 아무도 들으려 튜닝하지 않은 방송이었어
A wavelength dissolving into atmosphere
대기 속으로 녹아 사라지는 파장
The static holds the shape of what we said
잡음은 우리가 했던 말의 형체를 간직하고 있어
A forgotten frequency still ringing in my head
잊혀진 주파수가 아직도 내 머릿속에 맴돌아
The tower stands but nothing transmits anymore
송신탑은 서 있지만 더는 아무것도 보내지 않아
Just rust and rain collecting on the studio floor
그저 녹과 빗물이 스튜디오 바닥에 고여 있을 뿐
I found the reel still loaded in the deck
데크 안에 아직도 장착되어 있는 릴을 발견했어
Your voice preserved in dust and magnetic wreck
먼지와 자력의 잔해 속에 남은 네 목소리
And the wires remember what the world forgot
그리고 전선들은 세상이 잊은 것을 기억해
Every word still burning in a frequency left to rot
썩어가도록 방치된 주파수 속, 모든 단어들이 여전히 타올라
We were the broadcast no one tuned to hear
우리는 아무도 들으려 튜닝하지 않은 방송이었어
A wavelength dissolving into atmosphere
대기 속으로 녹아 사라지는 파장
The static holds the shape of what we said
잡음은 우리가 했던 말의 형체를 간직하고 있어
A forgotten frequency still ringing in my head
잊혀진 주파수가 아직도 내 머릿속에 맴돌아
We were the broadcast no one tuned to hear
우리는 아무도 들으려 튜닝하지 않은 방송이었어
A wavelength dissolving into atmosphere
대기 속으로 녹아 사라지는 파장
The static holds the shape of what we said
잡음은 우리가 했던 말의 형체를 간직하고 있어
A forgotten frequency still ringing in my head
잊혀진 주파수가 아직도 내 머릿속에 맴돌아
Still ringing in my head
아직도 내 머릿속에 맴돌아